William Allan Neilson Personal Papers, 1852-1946 RG 32.02.personal
Smith College Archives
- Series VI. WRITINGS, 1894-1946; 5.5 linear feet
  - Correspondence and News Clippings
    - The Harvard Classics: correspondence with Charles W. Eliot, 1909-1924 (Box 46, Folder 1041-42)
    - The Harvard Classics: correspondence, miscellaneous, 1922-1932 (Box 46, Folder 1043)
    - History of English Literature: correspondence, 1918-1931 (Box 46, Folder 1044-47)
    - Intellectual Honesty and Other Addresses (1940): news clippings (Box 46, Folder 1048)
    - The Junior Classics (1912): correspondence, 1913-1938 (Box 46, Folder 1049-51)
    - "Manual of Alumni Work": news clippings and press releases, 1924 (Box 46, Folder 1052)
    - Merriam-Webster Dictionary of Biography: minutes, 1938 (Box 46, Folder 1053)
    - Miscellaneous, 1903-1937; undated (Box 46, Folder 1054)
    - The Origins & Sources of the Court of Love (1899): correspondence, 1900-1930 (Box 46, Folder 1055)
    - Periodicals
      - Miscellaneous, 1903-1942 (Box 46, Folder 1056)
      - The Atlantic Monthly: correspondence, 1924-1938 (Box 46, Folder 1057)
      - Fashions of the Hour: correspondence, 1929-1930 (Box 46, Folder 1058)
      - Journal of Higher Education: correspondence, 1930-1937 (Box 46, Folder 1059)
      - The Nation: correspondence, 1922-1930 (Box 46, Folder 1060)
      - The New York Times: correspondence, 1931-1939 (Box 46, Folder 1061)
      - Saturday Review of Literature: correspondence, 1924-1942 (Box 46, Folder 1062)
      - Survey Graphic: correspondence, 1937-1939 (Box 46, Folder 1063)
    - Roads to Knowledge (1937): news clippings (Box 46, Folder 1064)
    - Roads to Knowledge (1937): correspondence, 1928-1937 (Box 46, Folder 1065-70)
    - Royalty statements: Houghton, Mifflin Co., 1917-1932 (Box 47, Folder 1071-72)
    - Royalty statements: MacMillan Co., 1921-1930 (Box 47, Folder 1073)
    - The Scottish Psalter (1927), Introduction by WAN: correspondence, 1926-1934 (Box 47, Folder 1074)
    - Selections from Chaucer (1921): correspondence, 1921-1938 (Box 47, Folder 1075)
    - Shakespeare's Works, Lake English Classics: correspondence, 1900-1923 (Box 47, Folder 1076-78)
    - Shakespeare's Works, Lake English Classics: statement of sales, 1915-1933 (Box 47, Folder 1079)
    - "Should Women Be Educated Like Men?": correspondence, 1929 (Box 47, Folder 1080)
    - Tudor Shakespeare (1911-1913): correspondence, 1919-1933 (Box 47, Folder 1081)
    - Types of English Literature (1907-?): correspondence and miscellaneous, 1904-1909; undated (Box 47, Folder 1082)
    - Webster's New International Dictionary, Second Edition (1934): advertisement, pamphlets (Box 47, Folder 1083)
    - Webster's New International Dictionary, Second Edition (1934): correspondence, 1924-45 (Box 47, Folder 1084-88)
    - Webster's New International Dictionary, Second Edition (1934):): news clippings - dinner to announce publication, 1934 June (Box 47, Folder 1089)
    - Volumes by WAN
      - Burns, How to Know Him (Box 47)
      - The Chief Elizabethan Dramatists Excluding Shakespeare (Box 47)
      - The City of Man: A Declaration of World Democracy (Box 47)
      - Essentials of Poetry (Box 47)
      - The Function of Higher Education with Carl Frederick White (Box 47)
      - A History of English Literature with Ashley Horace Thorndike (Box 47)
      - Intellectual Honesty and Other Addresses (Box 47)
      - Roads to Knowledge (Box 47)
      - Selections from Chaucer with Howard Rollin Patch (Box 47)
      - Years of Building by Caroline A. Yale, Introduction by WAN (Box 47)
      - Index to the Harvard Classics (Box 47)